var questions = [
  {
    answer: 1,
    question: "Who invented JavaScript?",
    option1: "Netscape",
    option2: "AOL",
    option3: "Microsoft",
    option4: "Nomadic Merchants from Tatoine",
  },
  {
    answer: 2,
    question:
      "What method would you use to remove the last element from an array?",
    option1: ".fitler()",
    option2: ".pop()",
    option3: ".map()",
    option4: ".getouttahere()",
  },
  {
    answer: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a semantic HTML tag?",
    option1: "<p>",
    option2: "<div>",
    option3: "<semantic>",
    option4: "<footer>",
  },
  {
    answer: 2,
    question:
      'Which code block would change the text color red for an HTML element with a "change-me" class?',
    option1: "#change-me{ color:red; }",
    option2: ".change-me{color:red;}",
    option3: "change-me{text-color:red;}",
    option4: ".change-me{just turn red please!}",
  },
  {
    answer: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is strict comparison?",
    option1: "!=",
    option2: "=",
    option3: "==",
    option4: "===",
  },
  {
    answer: 3,
    question: "Which selection will log something to the console",
    option1: "console.log",
    option2: "log.console()",
    option3: "console.log()",
    option4: "Abracadabra.Shout()",
  },
  {
    answer: 1,
    question: "Which most closely matches a function",
    option1: "A block of code called upon to perform a specific task",
    option2: "An object capable of storing multiple objects",
    option3: "An object based on a key pair dyanmic",
    option4: "The latest dance craze",
  },
  {
    answer: 4,
    question: "Which is not a JavaScript Data Type?",
    option1: "Boolean",
    option2: "Number",
    option3: "String",
    option4: "Thread",
  },
  {
    answer: 3,
    question: "What does DOM stand for?",
    option1: "Document Object Mode",
    option2: "Design Object Model",
    option3: "Document Object Model",
    option4: "Dominoes Order Meal",
  },
  {
    answer: 1,
    question: "What is this object type? var num =[1,2,3,4]",
    option1: "Array",
    option2: "Attribute",
    option3: "Beret",
    option4: "Function",
  },
];
